{"taskOID":40303,"originalTaskOID":40303,"setID":603,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questionElements":[{"questionID":4803,"questionDisplayText":"Service Need(s)","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need service? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answerElements":[{"answerID":717,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Air is drier than it should be","answerDisplayText":"Air is drier than it should be","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"CHECK_BOX","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":718,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Air is more moist than it should be","answerDisplayText":"Air is more moist than it should be","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"CHECK_BOX","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":5551,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"See/smell mold, mildew","answerDisplayText":"See/smell mold, mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"CHECK_BOX","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":3106,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Humidifier not getting water","answerDisplayText":"Humidifier not getting water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"CHECK_BOX","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":3107,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Humidifier using too much  water","answerDisplayText":"Humidifier using too much  water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"CHECK_BOX","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":6961,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wick/sponge pad is clogged or soldified","answerDisplayText":"Wick/sponge pad is clogged or soldified","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"CHECK_BOX","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":3815,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Metal grill caked with mineral deposits","answerDisplayText":"Metal grill caked with mineral deposits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"CHECK_BOX","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":6795,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Want to add air purifier","answerDisplayText":"Want to add air purifier","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"CHECK_BOX","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":6799,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want to add humistat","answerDisplayText":"Want to add humistat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"CHECK_BOX","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":6817,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Want to replace","answerDisplayText":"Want to replace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"CHECK_BOX","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":6601,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Unit needs cleaning/checking","answerDisplayText":"Unit needs cleaning/checking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"CHECK_BOX","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"CHECK_BOX","questionElements":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"DROP_LIST","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning & Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning & Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"DROP_LIST","questionElements":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"DROP_LIST","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"DROP_LIST","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"DROP_LIST","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"DROP_LIST","questionElements":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"RADIO_ONEPER_LINE","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"RADIO_ONEPER_LINE","questionElements":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"RADIO_SINGLE_LINE","questionElements":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"RADIO_SINGLE_LINE","questionElements":[]}]}]}